

# Tahir Ahmad

Gurudaspur,Natore,Rajshahi +8801610881871 tahirahmad0234@gmail.com https://tahirahmad.vercel.app/

Github: https://github.com/TahirAhmad01

My name is Tahir Ahmad. I am a web designer. Also, I am a React front-end developer. I have been doing web design for the last many years. I have worked in web design with HTML5, CSS3, CSS3 Animation, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, JQuery Animation, React. I am ready to convert your Html conversion ( PSD, image, pdf to Html ). I know many wonderful effects of use on websites and how to keep the website clean. Effective and clean cross-browser support has been a priority in many of the projects I've worked on.

# **Educational Background**

# **Rajshahi Polytechnic Institute** diploma in enginnering

session: 2019-20

#### **Skills & Proficiencies**

- Html
- Css
- Javascript
- Jquery
- Bootstrap
- React.js
- Redux

### Language

- Bangla
- English

# **Work Experience**

#### Kalpas inovation ltd.

React internship Dec 2021 - April 2021

#### **Volunteer Work & Certification**

#### Learn with sumit

Think in a react way August 2022 to septembar 2022

# **Projects list**

#### Weather applications using redux

This project is made with react, redux, and tailwind. This application takes your location access and gives your location weather. It gives current weather and also gives the next 24 hours' weather info. This application provides the next 10 days weather info. You can search for locations and see their weather.

**Live link**: https://weatherappredux.vercel.app/

# Github link:

https://github.com/TahirAhmad 01/WeatherAplication Redux

#### **Todo Application**

This project was made with react, firebase. If you are not logged in then it stores data in local storage. If you ate logged in then its fetches data from the firebase database. Before logging in if you add some data to local storage after logging in it will be synchronized with the firebase database.

**Live link**: https://todo-app-firebase-beta.vercel.app/ **Github link**: https://github.com/TahirAhmad01/todo-app